# **WAYNE GABULE**

ROGRAMMER MOTION GRAPHICS DESIGNER





**(**+63) 927 973 4717



wayne@gabule.com



Davao, Davao del Sur, Philippines



gabule.com

## **SKILLS**

- Java
- Spring Boot
- Flutter Dart
- C#
- Lua
- MySQL
- Git
- NextJS
- ReactJS
- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- Javascript
- HTML

- CSS
- Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap
- Figma
- Adobe After **Fffects**
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe
  - Premiere Pro
- Canva

## **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN** INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Ateneo de Davao University 2020-2024

### SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATE

Ateneo de Davao University

2018 - 2020

# CERTIFICATES

- Git Fundamentals
- TOPCIT Certification (Level 3)

## **PROFILE**

I am a recent BS in Information Technology graduate from Ateneo de Davao University with freelance experience in Java programming and video editing. I strive to excel in these fields, including motion graphics design, front-end development, and many more.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **ASSOCIATE ENGINEER 1**

July 2024 - Present

Orange & Bronze

- Implement features under the guidance of more senior developers, and in compliance with company & client practices.
- Allots time to learn software development practices & technologies as prescribed by the company and as needed by the client
- Contributes to ideas & plans of the team.
- Coordinates directly with client counterparts.

#### JAVA PLUGIN DEVELOPER

February 2020 - Present

Freelance

- Develop plugins (add-ons and modifications) for games such as Minecraft.
- · Able to work on and experience Java Programming and MySQL Database Management.
- Honed necessary skills for Object-Oriented Programming and Complex Database Logic and Queries.

#### ADMIN/VIDEO EDITOR

March 2023 - December 2024

Lava Automation

- In charge of all things video editing related, from video construction to motion graphic animation.
- · Helped create the company's current logo and have designed all of its animations, both 2D and 3D.
- Made infographics, PowerPoints, and similar graphic visualizations mainly for company advertisements.

# **PORTFOLIO**

<u>gabule.com</u>

behance.net/alphazed1

wg-portfolio.vercel.app